Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
翻译 by 猪仔钱盎
字幕根据网络英字翻译制作 仅用于个人交流 请勿用于商业行为 一切后果由使用者负责
I'll never forget my time
here as a Hillford girl.
在Hillford读书的日子仍记忆犹新
It's so wonderful to be back.
能够再次回来看看真的很开心
Thank you.
谢谢大家
As school captain of Hillford,
身为HILLFORD的学生主席
I'd like to thank Mrs Dorothy Watson
and Mrs Iris McKenna
我要十分感谢Dorothy Watson女士
和Iris McKenna女士
for coming to talk to us today as
part of our Centenary Celebrations.
在学校百年庆之际与大家分享美好回忆
Iris师姐.敢情的,
To meet the oldest surviving
Hillford girl is a privilege.
能见识您这位算是活得最久的Hillford校友
真是荣幸无比
I'd now like to introduce
to the stage my Year 12 prefects
现在我十分荣幸地为大家请上台的是
wearing the uniforms of
the last 100 years of Hillford.
穿着过去历经百年变迁的本校各款校服的
高三学生会干事们
From Morgan in the uniform of
yesteryear
从Morgan身上最古老的款式
all the way through to me, wearing
the familiar uniform of today.
一直延伸到我身上这件你我身上的最新款
We would now like to thank the ladies
接下来我们将以之前精心准备的
by showing them
our dance presentation
舞蹈表演来给予这些美好的设计
that we prepared especially for them.
最诚恳的致敬
Hi. My name's Ja'mie.
大家好，我叫Ja'mie
I used to be Jamie,
but I added the apostrophe in Year 8.
本名应该是Jamie，
但在初三的时候我就私自强加了个单引号
I'm 17 years old.
我今年17岁
I live in Sydney, Australia.
我家住澳大利亚的悉尼
And I'm a private school girl.
我在女私校读书
This series is about
my last few months of school
这个短剧是在展示我高中毕业前
and the events
that changed my life forever.
那些成为我人生转捩点的
最后几个月的人和事
We're the most expensive
girls' school in the State.
我们是本郡最贵的女子私校
The most expensive?
我们有那么贵么？
Yeah, we are.
当然啊
It is, we are.
我们真的最贵
Yeah, and we top the State
academically as well.
而且哦我们教育评级也是最强大的
Yeah, that's because of
the Asian factor. Yeah.
那还得多谢学校的亚裔生
They're all on scholarships.
她们全都拿奖学金的要知道
There's heaps of Asians here.
我们学校确实贼多亚洲人
Hillford's pretty much known
Hillford最出名的自然是
for having the hottest girls
in the whole of Sydney.
我们囊括全悉尼最正的妹子们
It's like a known thing.
这都算是常识了拜托
Yeah. Yeah.
嗯~嗯~
If you go to Hillford, people are like
'Oh, my God. You must be so hot.'
就像你说你来自Hillford，别人就会说“叼呀 你实靓爆镜”
（无责任粤语是猪一贯的字幕作风 以下不时出现 请见谅）
I'm not even bragging but me and
my friends are all pretty much quiche.
恬不知耻地说我和我这班姐妹们quiche到没朋友~
（quiche-一种烘焙的蛋挞，这里主角利用这个食物自身的温度
来和常作性感一词的HOT做比较 猪就不乱译了 直接引用 后面多次出现）
Like, if you couldn't tell
from looking at us.
不过这眼睁睁的大事实其实也不用点明了，不是么？
Oh, if you didn't know 'quiche'
is a word that I made up.
对了，或许你们不了我说的quiche，
那是我自创的用词
It basically means 'hot'
but, like, it's a step above 'hot'.
就和性感的hot的意思差不多
但你懂的，它就是比hot再高温那么一点点
It's, like, more than just hot.
就是，你了的，比hot在给力那么一点点~
No, I'd say basically quiche
is hot to the point
我真心觉得quiche就是最能说明正点的一种hot（双关 热度|性感）了
where you wanna have sex with them.
尤其当那种热度带来的口感高潮占领一切的时候。
（这里只能意译，猪能力不够）
Rootable.
从宇宙根源学上说
Like, there's hot
and then there's quiche.
就好比这里要是hot的状态
那么这里就是quiche了
One of the main measures of
quicheness is your box gap.
要知道作为衡量你的quiche指数的标准
就是你的股间距了
Yeah, box gap.
对 没错
Basically what it is, is, like...
Maybe you could pop up, Immy.
简单来说就是指..
Immy不如你来给演示一下吧
You don't want the thighs
to touch at all,
你绝不该让两边粘合在一起
so you want sort of like
at least a three finger,
标准应该最少有三个手指的间距
and I'll just demonstrate that.
就像我现在比量的这个
The more, the better basically.
而且 平心而论
If you've got your thighs rubbing
together from fat
你是因为肥胖而造就不够间距
then you need to think
about what you're eating
那我们建议要好好考虑节食了
or maybe just accept the fact
that you'll never be quiche.
再不是就是面对你quiche不起来的现实吧
We should do, like,
a mega sleepover at my house.
我建议我们不如都到我家来个华丽丽地过夜吧
- Ja'mie's like our leader.
-Ja'mie是我们的大姐大
- We're all prefects.
-我们都是学生会的
That's what brought us
together this year. We're all BFFs.
所以造就我们今年的相识和最终的结义金兰
I had a different friend group
last year
我去年其实还有另一个小圈子的
but I had to get rid of them because
但我也只能忍痛脱离她们
Brianna, my bestie,
kind of got really weird and fat.
因为我那亲Brianna不知怎的越来越奇葩圆润了
She's kind of a bit indie now.
Yeah...
她现在也有点挺特立独行的
大概..
I'm still really nice if I see them
around the playgrounds.
但当我在操场喜见她们我还是会热脸相迎的
Hi, Ja'mie.
Hi.
Oh, my God. Awkies.
妖~吐艳~好尴尬~
Sometimes it's better to kind
of let your friends go, in a way.
有些人有时还是得更潇洒的看待友谊嘛
- You need to move on.
- 不要再纠缠旧感情了
- Move on.
- 不要再认亲认戚了
I'm the school captain. So I'm like
the boss of the whole school.
我这学生会主席就相当于全校的大姐大
Um, and this is my team, my prefects.
这些是我的队友，我的好学生会妹妹们
We're family.
我们就是一家人
Hi.
跟大家打声招呼吧
OK, guys, let's set up here.
来~姐妹们，让我们站两列
So every morning, we do gate duty.
每天早上，我们都要站校门岗
So we have the ability
to give out Friday detentions.
而且能给违纪的同学周五留堂处分
Phone off and in your locker.
You're on school grounds.
记得关手机和一定要锁在私人柜里
要知道你们已经走进校园领域内了哦
Write her name down.
What's her name?
记下她名字
她叫啥来着？
Three warnings and you get a Friday.
三次记过你就要周五留堂了哦
No wristbands in school.
在校不给戴这个
- No coffee on school grounds.
-校道内不许喝着咖啡
- Oh, wow.
I feel like a lot
of the younger girls
我能感觉到其实很多低年级的妹妹
really look up to us though.
是很崇拜我们的
Get your mum to sort that out,
Celeste.叫你妈妈好好帮你整理一下
I've spoken to you before about this.
我记得之前就跟你提过这事了
Get that pink shit off your bag.
Take it off.
你书包上那粉瞎的鬼东西给我撤了
This is the prefect room
这里是学生会的专属间
so this is like the room
where us as prefects chill out.
这里就是我们姐妹们舒展的好地方
It's a prefect-only zone.
别人是不许进的
Excuse me, can you get away
from the prefect room entrance?
不好意思，能麻烦你们给学生会入口让出个道么
Move, away from the entrance.
快~别挡着碍眼
I mean, being in year 12,
it's such a stressful year.
我想说高三真不是给人过
We've got a mat and stuff and we do
yoga some mornings and just chill.
我们要是在早上不执勤找几个垫子让咱们好好做个瑜伽
放松放松那该多好
Yeah. It's really good.
啊 你一说我就点赞了
I can't believe I've got
a whole day ahead of me.
一想到还有一天的课我就 怒CRY
Did the cleaners vacuum this or not?
话说那清洁工到底吸尘了没啊
Like, there's something about being
a prefect that feels really good.
要知道 其实做学生会的感觉还是挺爽的
I always knew I wanted to be one.
我很早就立志要成为其中一员了
Totes. I definitely knew I was going
to be one from, like, Year7.
绝逼的，我那啥 初一时就已经密谋要当了
And we all have the Prefect Promise
that Ja'mie made up.
我们还有Ja'mie帮我们订立的学生会盟约
The Prefect Promise.
噢~说到盟约啊~
Basically, the Prefect Promise
is like a promise
简单来说吧 盟约的主旨就是
that we'll all, like, stick together,
as prefects, no matter what happens.
一日成军 终日一体
Yeah, like a family...
Any bad stuff that like goes down...
对 我们就是一家亲
家人有难
..then, we'll be there for each
other.
绝对一同共度
For example, if one of us got depression
and wanted to, like, kill themselves
打比方说 如果我们其中一人抑郁了
接着想自杀的说
then as part of the Prefect Promise,
we'd probably all kill ourselves.
根据盟约 我们就要集体自杀
Yeah.
噢~
Like.
类似的~对~
I didn't know it was that extreme.
我们要走得那么极端么~
Yeah, it is.
当然要 ，我说的算
Have a good first period, everyone!
I'm gonna miss you guys.
亲~第一课时要好好的哦~
我会想乃们的~
I love you, Ja'mie, so much.
Ja'mie，我爱死你了
Have the best time in English.
You too.
好好享受英文课哦~
你们也要好好的哦~
I'm the leader. I'm sort of like
the mother hen of the group, you could say.
我是会长，自然就是大家的好姐姐 好慈母~之类的~
Like, I have to look
after my little chickens.
她们就是我护翅下的小鸡们~
Send me anything.
记得给我捎个信什么的~
Send me selfies, just whatevs.
Snapchat me.
自拍啊~私信啊~语音~啥都好~
All of you, I fucking love you.
我绝B爱死你们了
I love you, Ja'mie.
爱你哦 Ja'mie
I fucking love you.
我艹B地爱着你们
I miss you, guys.
我会想乃们的
I love all of you.
你们什么的 我最爱了
What I'm seeing now, I fucking love.
你们是啥~你们就是我的爱~
- Mwah!
-啵个~
- See you at recess.
-课间休息见了
The usual spot.
老地方不见不散
- Bye.
- Oh, my God.
我哭~
- ILY.
我爱你们的缩合
- ILY!
ILY. Love you.
ILY 我爱你
Bye!
要走了哦
Maddie, I'm really sad already.
Maddie 我已经开始悲想你了
Aww.
I can't go.
我不行了
Aww!
I fucking love you.
我绝B爱你
Oh, my God, you're my best friend.
你知道么 你是我独一无二的蜜闺
Like, two hours.
乖~就两小时嘛~
I'm being an idiot,
I'm being an idiot.
我失态了
- It's alright.
- 我理解
- We'll go.
- 我们真的要走了
Bye.
贵安哦
Text me any goss.
记得私信我
Bye.
Bye, we love you.
（总之就是要说爱你和再见和不舍 猪我受够了！
不翻了一下类似句子自己脑补去）
I really love you. Seriously. Bye.
And Ja'mie's, like, an all-rounder.
你们要知道JA'MIE是全能精英
Pretty much.
Basically, she's good at everything.
真心的 她什么都很强大
Yeah.
可不是么~
I don't think there's
any other way to put it.
我都不知道还有什么别的形容词了
Guilty.
好吧~我认了~
Yeah, I've got the most Facebook
friends in the whole school. Yay.
我吧~无非就是全校脸书朋友最多的那个拉~
Look at her blazer.
Like, there's just so much on it.
看那些课外活动的胸标
Yeah, I know,
I'm good at a lot of stuff.
没法啦~
谁叫我有精力有能力呢
I'm good at sport.
运动就不在话下罗
When I say 'fast', I don't mean
knock me out of the fucking boat.
当我喊快点的时候，
我不是叫你们给我晃得我胃都快吐出来了
I'm creatively amazing.
我创作也俱佳啦
It feels really balanced now.
现在我能感觉到所谓的宇宙守恒了
The performing arts. I'm
really good at the performing arts.
说到百老汇，噢~我独立鹤群了我~
I love it here.
I really, really love it here.
我思故我在
我思便是故我在~
And basically, what I like to say,
这样说吧~用我常用来形容自己的
'cause my name's Ja'mie,
I like to say I'm j'amazing.
因为我叫洁咪~所以我就是杰出无比~咪~~~
And Ja'mie is so
caring and giving. Seriously.
其实JA'MIE还很有爱心，是真的
Yeah. I'm really caring.
也对啦~我是挺善良的
Like, I'm really good at raising
money for the less fortunate.
要知道我的一个强项就是为不幸的人筹款了
You know, like, we go around
the playground quite a lot
你懂得，就像啊 我一走到游憩区的时候
and I sort of have an ability to be
able to get money out of people.
那些善款就会像有脚似的走上门了
Fuck off. They're for charity.
别闹 这是做善事用的！懂不
If I see someone in need,
I want to give back to them.
当我见到有人需要帮助 我就会帮
That's such a good quality.
这是你一大优点啊
It's a charity thing and
I'm going out to the Western Suburbs
就像之前我去了西郊区
to this really povo area
where these African immigrants live,
那边都是非洲移民的平民窟
and it's really cute.
那个社区还很萌呢
Hi, everyone!
乃们好哦~亲
Basically, I read to them
and I just chill with them
基本上 我就是给他们读读书啊
分享一下人生的美好啊
and hang out, play basketball,
whatever's going.
还有就顺势玩个篮球啊什么的
Try and stop me.
来拦我哦~
Come on.
来嘛
Oh, soz, soz.
噢~对不啾~对不啾
（猪自创对不起哦的连音,自己脑补一下吧）
And there's some really quiche boys
there too.
不得不说那边还是很多quiche的男生的
Cheese.
茄子
They're really povo
but they look really fit
他们真的很平民窟
但是他们身材都是夯夯的
and have, like, hard abs.
想什么胸肌啊 二头肌啊 什么肌肌啊~
（噗嗤 猪忍不住就这样翻了）
- In a rough kind of way.
- Because they're not eating.
- 只能从精壮的层面说哦
- 谁叫他们吃不饱呢
Oh, my God.
So cute.
噢~卡哇伊~~
太萌了~~
This is the Hillford Medallist
honour board
这个就是Hillford荣誉学生奖牌榜
and basically what it is, it's all
the girls that have won the Hillford Medal
就是说过去一百年里所有曾经得过荣誉奖牌的女生
for the last 100 years.
的名字都在这里哦
Um, and it's this really prestigious
award that they give out to, like,
这个奖是校内最受瞩目敬仰的的头衔
the most amazing girl
from Year 12 of that year and stuff.
获奖的均是高三的杰出女青年
Like, you've got to be good
at everything.
总之就是要各项全能的人才才能得到
This is the girl that won it last
year.
这里挂的是去年的得奖者
She's not even that hot.
她都还不能谈得上貌美如花呢
Yeah, but you're definitely going
to win the Hillford Medal this year.
可不是 但是今年你就肯定无走鸡了
Oh, yeah.
没错哦
I probably will.
我还真有可能呢~
Seriously, who else
are they going to give it to?
好啦~别开玩笑了
你们还有别的名单么
They wouldn't give it to anyone else.
That's the thing.
不可能还有别人能跟你比啦
Imagine me in this frame, guys.
亲们 想象一下这里将有我的画像
It looks so right.
太对头了
Oh, my God.
美CRY了~
Ja'mie!
I totes nearly smashed it.
我天啊 我差点就把人家给毁了
I am so random. I can't believe
I just did that. Sorry.
我好害羞，人家不该这样做的 对不起嘛
So this is the new Centenary Centre.
这里是新综合大楼
It's like amazing art classrooms
and stuff. It's really cool.
将会建有华丽丽的艺术专业科室什么的
萌翻了
And they're getting this sculpture
thing out the front
还有就是门庭广场前的铜铸像了
and they're getting this really
famous sculpture guy to do it.
听说还是请大师来雕刻哦
And it sort of like represents
the ultimate Hillford girl.
为的是展示最典型的本校女生
Yeah, and Ms Welham announced the
other day
Welham老师那天还说只要谁赢了今年的
that the Hillford Medal winner
Hillford荣誉学生奖牌
is gonna be the girl
that's in the sculpture so...
谁就是这个铜像的原型模特了
You're gonna look so good in bronze.
I know.
我觉得铜色最适合你的五官了
Oh, my God!
想想就萌翻了
I know.
我也觉得
I've got to work out
what pose I'll do,
我可要开始想到时候摆什么姿势了
'cause it kinda lasts forever
and it's going to, like...
因为这可是要一直让众生膜拜到永远啊
I'm thinking maybe, like, I
don't want to do that walking thing.
我之前就有想说 我绝对不要做这种什么行走状
No.
不要 对
I want to sort of...
我想呢~就这...样...
What about my hands kind of
back a bit like that?
要不这种手稍微向后摆什么的？
Maybe on one hip?
要不插个腰？
On your hip, yeah.
对像这样
Yeah!
对~就是这样
That in bronze
will be fucking amazing.
艹~这姿势配上铜色 绝B美到没朋友
Yeah.
Seriously.
我说真的
Thank you, Hillford!
母校万岁~
Oh, my God. Seriously, I'm praying
that someone videoed it.
姐妹们 我说啊 我求爷爷求奶奶
刚才要有人给我拍下来啊
I think I saw Hannah had her phone
up. I know she had it.
我好像看到Hannah举起她的手机了
对 我就知道她会拍
Oh, my God. What about
when you did the slut drop?
你知道么 你刚才的M字腿赞B了
Girls, girls, I saw the dance.
The gesture is great.
同学同学 我刚才看了你们的表演
我觉得动作很流畅
But we've got to be careful that
in delivery there's nothing inappropriate.
但是不是要注意一下不要太过火了呢
-There wasn't.
没有啊
-In the first place,
we start with uniforms.
在一开始的时候是得体的
I want them done up now.
但最好就一直得体下去
There is to be no undergarments
seen at any time.
我决不允许任何内衣部分外露的情况出现
Buttons done up.
扣子一定要扣好
You can't even see anything.
这样根本没有露内衣啊
OK. And the other thing...
Excuse me. The other thing is
好了 还有
那个听着 还有一件事
we need to get rid of some of those
more risque dance movements.
你们还试着删减一下潜在问题的动作
But sir... They were totally
into it. Those women loved it.
我明白你说的 校长 但是，要知道她们其实
挺喜欢我们的表演的啊
Those dance moves are OK
for things like schoolies.
如果这是毕业典礼 我也就算啦
Do you know how much work
we put into that dance?
你知道我们练了多久么
I can see that.
That's not the issue.
我能理解
但是这不是问题的核心
The issue is the way in which
you represent the school.
问题是你们的一举一动都代表着我校
You are young women
representing Hillford Girls Grammar.
你们就是学校 学校就是你们
I'm not here
to negotiate what goes on.
总之我说了不许就是不许
There is a line, and we mustn't
cross it in the future.
我现在说得很明白了 以后一定要注意
Alright.
Are we clear on that?
-好吧
-明白了吗?
Sorry, sir.
明白了校长
Alright, girls. Off to class.
好的 那么现在去乖乖上课
Quick, let's go.
快 解散
We won't do it again, sir.
我们下次不敢了 校长
Make sure you don't.
知错就好
We won't.
知道的哦
Bye, sir.
校长 再见
Bye.
再见
Oh, my fucking God. Seriously,
why are you even looking at my bra?
艹他没天理 什么不知廉耻嘛
那你还不是往我胸罩里盯
Obviously, his wife's
not giving him what he wants.
我肯定他老婆没有好好给他泄欲
Seriously, why are you looking
at my tits? It's so awkies.
说真的 你有本事别看人家的凸点啊~
吐艳死了
It's like you're 60.
老古董 不知丑
Immy. I saw your new DP.
It's so quiche.
Immy 我看到你新微博的照片了
太TMD的quiche了
So good.
Did you take that in Chem?
太美了
你在CHEM那边拍的？
Did you know your Facebook status
is 'I love pussy'?
你知道你先在脸书的状态是：我爱你个B
Guys, cray clouds.
Look at the clouds. I'm gramming.
姐妹们 彩云~快看天边一朵云
我来给拍下来
We should do a groupie.
我们来群拍~~
Yeah! Yes.
好啊~~
Morgan, take it.
Morgan你来抓机子
Three, two, one.
三二一
Well, at school, I'm
pretty much friends with everyone.
要知道 我是学校大家的好朋友
Like, everyone thinks
I'm really nice.
每个人都特爱我
I'm gonna get a photo of the Asians.
Oh, my goodness.
我一定要拍那边的亚洲妹子们
太萌了
I think, as school captain,
我很标榜自己作为学生会会长
that's a really good thing for me
to be the cray ambassador of niceness.
就一定要成为大家的亲善大使
Hello! Hello!
嘿·嘿
Oh, my God.
太搞了
I'm gonna gram it.
I'm going to hashtag 'fried rice'.
我要微博它
接着标签为‘炒饭’
I'm so random!
我太不识相了
But YOLO.
但是就是很萌
Oh, stop it!
妖~不要啦
Like, I've got my BFFs,
你瞧 我姐妹一堆
but I'm nice to pretty much everyone
in the school, except the boarders.
但我基本来说还是人见人爱的 除了对着那些寄宿生
Hi, Lauren! Hi, boarders.
嘿Lauren 寄宿生们你们好哦
Oh, my God.
How are you going?
天啊
你们今天过得可好
How's the boarding house? Looks fun.
宿舍可好？萌不？
You guys got changed really quickly.
你们这身装还换得挺快的哦
I like how you just get into the
school jersey straight after school.
我特么欣赏你直接课后就套运动服
The boarders are these girls,
right, they live at the school
这些寄宿妹子 基本因为家是务农的还是之类的
and they're from like farms and
stuff.
就偏远只好住校
Like, they're rich but they're,
like, really kind of rural
她们就一爆发户
土气是甩不掉的
and all of them
are pretty much lesbians.
还有我想她们都应该是女同
So, what are you having
for dinner tonight?
你们晚餐想好了么
Lesbianese food or...?
Ja'mie, you're so funny.
-女同餐还是？
-Ja'mie你太贱了
So is it true that you guys
are all vagitarians?
话说你们是不是真的就都是素食者啊
Oh, my God. That is so mean.
矮油 太贱了啦
How fat is Erin?
Disgusting.
Erin你瞧她那身段
太恶了吧也
She's put on so much weight.
Put down the fucking fork.
她吃太多了啦
好心她就别老端着碗筷不放啦
She looks fucking ridiculous. It's like
someone has pumped her up or something.
她看上去好傻B 就像给人打过气似的
Hey, Erin, have you lost weight
lately? You look really good.
喂~Erin你最近是不是瘦了 看上去变美了
Need a tampon, Ja'mie?
'Cause you're being a fucking bitch.
你来大姨妈了？JA’mie
难怪你一副贱相
Oh, why? Do you wanna stick it in me?
Heavy.
你想帮我塞卫生棉么？
肥婆
I don't even know
why I don't like them.
其实我也不知道为什么我就是不喜欢她们
It's just like... they're just really
annoying. You know what I mean?
总之呢 她们看着就闹心 你了的
They're sort of, like, fat and weird
and they have stupid haircuts.
你瞧瞧她们那身段啊 恶心啊还有那傻不溜秋的发型
You know, it's like...
you're a girl, act like one.
你们不是女孩子么 就不懂得洁身自好啊
Hey, boarders, like,
you know, on farms,
嘿 寄宿生 你们在农场啊
do you have to have, like,
a licence to drive a tractor?
开卡车到底要不要执照啊
I seriously wanna know.
我真心想知道嘢
Do you have tiny tits
for any particular reason, Ja'mie?
那我问你那颗粒般小的的奶头
是不是什么病啊，JA'MIE
First of all, why the fuck
are you looking at my tits anyway?
首先 我要说你干嘛看人家的奶头！
More proof that you're a lesbian.
说你就是女同志了吧！
And, secondly, shut the fuck up
or I'll give you a Friday detention.
接着你再给我乱吼我就给你记过留堂
Don't ever bag Ja'mie's tits.
Yeah.
别给人家乱吼Ja'mie的奶头
就是
The reason they're small
is because I had a eating disorder
我奶头小是因为人家有饮食紊乱
so it's not exactly a laughing
matter, OK?
你怎么将自己的开心建立在别人的痛苦之上
So go fucking fist yourself.
去吃你妈的草皮蛋
Alright, horse face. I will.
我会的 婊子妓女脸
Fucking bitch. Give me that.
草你个婊子 递你那个给我
Here, take it, take it.
来接着接着
Fucking slut!
草死你个婊子
Fucking bitch.
死婊子
Ja'mie, Ja'mie! Elliott老师在.
You got a Friday, by the way.
I'm writing it up.
你周五走不掉了！我铁定记你过
What's going on here?
怎么了孩子们
Hi, miss.
老师好
The Year 7s
are throwing food and stuff.
没啥 初一生他们随地乱扔杂物
Don't worry. I'll sort it out.
I'll get them to clean it up.
不用担心 我会管教她们收拾的
Alright.
真乖
See you, miss.
老师再见
Year 7s, get up.
Go and fucking clean up the milk.
初一的 给我起来
好好给我清干净那些牛奶渍
And don't throw food around.
Pick it up. Hurry up.
以后别给我再乱扔了 知道不
快清
Oh, my God. That was so Year 7.
就是啊 真没规矩的初一生
See you, Lauren.
Lauren 回见哦
Enjoy checking out my arse
as I walk away.
我转身离去的倩影你也不要放过哦
Oh, my God.
哈 你太强了
Well, after school, like,
if we don't have sport or whatever,
接着一如往常 如果我们没有课外活动的话
then we usually go to the bus stop.
That's like the place to go.
我们一般会跑去巴士站附近
那可好了
It's just down the road
out the front of Kelton Boys Grammar
最重要那里就是在Kelton男校的校门旁
and, like, me and the girls,
we know heaps of Kelton guys,
我还有姐妹们可是有很多男校的蜜闺什么的呢
so it's just really good to chill.
所以绝对是个好去处
News? Goss? Go.
八卦？趣闻？快说
Oh, my God.
等个嘛~
How was the dance? Was it cray?
你们那群舞怎样？华丽丽么？
Oh, my God. It was so legit.
Ja'mie looked so quiche.
潮爆了 我给你说
JA'MIE是万人焦点啊
Seriously, I went like full slutty,
I had like my buttons undone
你要知道 我跳得可骚了
我将扣子都一字排开
and then Hayes afterwards busted me
for showing too much cleavage.
接着就被校长说东说西的了
But, seriously, he wants me so badly.
但他明显就是想吃了我那副死相
Yeah, you can tell.
对啊 真恶心
Yeah, I reckoned he like full jizzed
while I was dancing.
我敢肯定我一边跳他一边鼓鼓地支帐篷了都
Is he hot? Like silver fox or...?
Um, no. He's chat as.
-他帅不？是宽叔款还是...
-哪有 就一老宅男
Oh, my God. That's disgusting.
娘亲的 太恶了吧
I think it's important
as a girl of my age
我真心觉得就我现在的花样年华
and also my status within the school
as school captain to socialise,
还有作为母校学生会主席的身份来说
especially with the other
elite private schools.
交际。尤其是和其他等级别的精英私校的互动是
必不可少
So Kelton, like, the guys there,
拿Kelton男校来说吧
like, they're the future leaders of
the country, if you know what I mean.
你要知道那边的学生可各个都会是将来的达官贵人啊
So, like, as me, it's good for me
to sort of get in with them now
所以呢 小妮子我现在要是能和他们好好处处
so in the future, I'll have, like,
connections for later in life.
不久将来就能各种人脉广布啦
Oh, my God.
I do have goss from today.
噢 娘亲的 我想起今天有啥可爆料的了
There is a major hottie in Year 10
that's just started.
今年刚来了个高一绝色萌男新生
A rugby scholarship guy,
and he is so fucking quiche.
橄榄队成员 所以quiche得一B
I'm getting, like, a semi
just thinking about it.
就光想想 我就半高潮了
Year 10. That is so adorbs.
I love Year 10s.
高一师弟 噢~太萌了 高一赛高啊
So is he legit quiche?
他quiche得合理么？
He's definitely quiche.
绝对正宗口味哦
And he is fully your type, babes.
He's got bushy eyebrows.
他绝对是你杯茶啊 亲
尤其你喜欢浓眉大眼的
He's a bit meatheady, a hot face
though, and, like, massive feet.
他有点胸大无脑 但胜在有萌脸 接着
还是大脚丫
And you know, he seems pretty dumb.
就是你懂得 典型四肢发达头脑简单就对了
He sounds fucking incredible.
他太TMD对我胃口了
You've got to arrange a meeting.
你帮奴家牵个线啦~
Oh, my God, Ja'mie. He's in Year 10.
天啊 JA'MIE 人家是高一小男生嘢
Um, care factor. I fucking love
Year 10s. They're hot as.
人家御姐爱正太啊 正太赛高
Who's he friends with?
Like, Josh and that?
他扎哪个堆啊
JOSH那堆么？
-He's been chilling with Josh all
day.
对啊 他整天就跟着JOSH混就对了
-I'll ask the Year 10s.
姐我直接找个高一来问
Um, excuse me.
Are you guys in Year 10?
嗨~你好 请问你高一的学生么
Um, do you know
the new rugby scholarship guy?
那个你认识新来的那个橄榄队男生不？
Um, what's his name?
他叫什么名字
Mitchell.
Hot name.
Like, bushy eyebrows.
好MAN的名字
额~他浓眉大眼
Kind of meatheady. Bit stupid.
四肢发达 头脑简单
Is he friends with Josh McLaughlin?
Yeah.
你确定他跟Josh McLaughlin是抱团的对吧?
素的
He's totally coming. Look, quick.
There he is with Josh.
那不用问了 看 快 人家正和JOSH一起走出来呢
Oh, my fucking God,
the guy on the right?
噢~哈雷路亚~走右边那个么？
Seriously, fuck my life.
He's so fucking quiche.
草啊！我融化了 他太TM的quiche了！
Oh, my God, guys.
天啊 快疯了
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
I'm going to talk to him.
草草草草草草草
我一定要和他对上话
Yeah go for it.
He's so hot, Ja'mie.
对啊 JA'MIE 上啊
不要放过他就对了
Alright. Your school captain
is going to do some socialising.
姐妹们 你们的学生会主席要变身交际大丽花啦~
YOLO.
Go, Ja'mie!
加油~
干巴爹~
Hi. Mitchell? Hi, I'm Ja'mie.
你好啊~Mitchell 偶叫Ja'mie呀
I'm school captain
of Hillford Girls Grammar.
我是Hillford女校学生会主席
Just wanted to welcome you
to the area and stuff.
我就是想代表我校来跟问候一下
希望你会喜欢我们的这区的生活哦
Um... so, rugby scholarship?
额。。。那个~你橄榄队哦~
That's pretty cool.
太帅了
Yeah, it's cool.
对啊 帅爆哦
Yeah, I can tell you look really
sporty and stuff so, yeah...
那个 我都感觉得到你那健硕体态的气场了 呀~
Really good to meet you. Just wanted to
sort of say hi, welcome and all that.
那就先这样？我就是想过来跟你说声HI
还有就是关怀一下新生之类的
So if you want to know anything about
Hillford, then just chat with me.
那个如果你有些什么关于我校的问题 不要客气
尽管找我哦
Ja'mie. Your mum's here!
Ja'mie.你妈来接了
Fuck my life!
叼佢
I told you fucking 3:10,
not 3:0-fucking-7. Fucking bitch.
我不是跟你说3：10么！07分的时候你出现个毛啊
贱人
Um, sorry, Mitchell, I've got to go,
but really good meeting you.
Mitchell，不好意思 我娘来接了
总之很高兴认识你
Hopefully, see you around here
and stuff. Um, bye.
期待下次还能碰面罗~
Love you so much.
爱你
I love you so much.
爱死你
Love you so much.
爱
I love you so fucking much.
爱死
I'm going to miss you.
想你哦
I love you.
爱你哦
Bye.
I love you so much.
爱爱爱爱~
I love you too.
乖哦
Bye. ILY everyone, ILY.
走罗~爱爱爱爱爱爱爱爱爱（烦不烦）
Bye!
Madison and Olivia are staying over.
So thanks.
Madison和Olivia今晚来我们家留宿
以上
Oh.哦
Um, what do I do?
好~接下来我该怎么搞~
You press the button
and you got to have the key in first.
你按个按钮 接着记得先插上钥匙
OK. Shut up, I know what I'm doing.
够~停~我了我该怎么做
Jamie, you have to drive the car.
You have to focus now.
Jamie 你要驾车了 所以你要好好留心周遭
You put your windscreen wipers on,
not your indicator.
你把雨刮给开了
而不是指示灯
Why do they put it on the same side
as the indicator?
为什么这车要设计成两种控制在同一区啊
OK, I'm going, drive, here we go.
啊~不管了 走起
Jamie, have you checked
your blind spot?
Jamie你检查了倒后镜没
Why isn't it going?
为什么它不动啊
Because the handbrake is still on.
因为你忘记放手闸
Well, take the fucking handbrake off.
那你干嘛不给我放了它啊
I told you to take it off
before I get in. It's annoying.
我一上车就叫你帮我松了啊 真烦
Jamie, we've had this discussion
before.
Jamie我们之前谈得好好的
If you're not confident in driving
then you're not allowed to drive.
如果你没能力开 我就不该让你来开
Soz, I thought that was the
accelerator.
对不啾~我踩错刹车当油门了
For heaven's sake, this is ridiculous.
I want you girls to keep quiet.
天啊 这咋整啊 你们后座的能不能先别吵啊
Oh, my God...
How hot is Mitchell.
天啊 Mitchell就一秀色可餐啊
Oh, my God, he is so quiche.
对啊他绝对quiche啊
When I first saw him I was like,
'Oh, my God.'
要知道第一眼我见他
我就直接萌晕了
He's got the eyebrows,
he's got the best body.
他那浓眉毛
他那六头肌
Oh, my God.He's, like,
really mature for his age.
他那血气方刚啊
Seriously,
I cannot stop thinking about him.
说真的 我无法忘怀啊
Please watch on
the side of the road again.
求你好好看路况
Courtney, move so Madison
can get her fucking seatbelt on.
Courtney滚一边去好让Madison能扣上安全带
He looks really, like,
mysterious and stuff.
他越看就越给力啊
Fucking little bitch. Grow some tits.
死妹子 奶头都未长齐
Don't speak to your sister like
that! You can't talk, flatty.
你不许这样说你妹妹
肥婆
Courtney 你也不许回嘴
I've got bigger tits than you
and when I was in year 7,
我在你这年纪的时候我奶头就已经成人了
my tits were fucking way bigger
than yours.
总之是永远比你的贼大！
They were only fucking mosquito
bites. I've got mangoes.
你那就两个蚊叮的包
我那两颗是芒果懂不！
You are going to have the smallest
tits an adult has ever had
你啊就等着做一辈子全世界奶头最小的
in the whole fucking world because
you're a fucking little bitch.
混帐婊子好了
Jamie, I'm going to tell
your father about this.
Jamie我要向你爹告状了哦
I am trying to drive
while that little bitch
我可是好心顺路载这丫
is preventing my friend
from wearing her safety device.
但她却不给我朋友安全出行的权利嘢
Do you think I want you as a sister?
You're so fucking irritating!
我真不知为什么我倒八百辈的霉了
有你这讨人嫌的姐姐
The world doesn't evolve around you.
世界不是围着你转的
Want me to slap you
when I get home?
你想我回家立马给你一巴掌是不？
You can't 'cause I'm faster than you.
滚你去吧 我出手永远比你快
Shut the fuck up while I'm driving.
在我开车的时候给我闭嘴
Jamie, you drive.
Courtney, please behave yourself.
Jamie好好开车
Courtney你也不要闹了
Whatevs! I'm the boss of the car.
I'm driving.
够了！我现在是司机
我做主
With two hands.
手不离盘
I want to talk about Mitchell.
我只想讨论萌物
I should totally add him on Facebook.
我绝对要加他微博
Oh, my God, I'm going to add him.
'Cause he'll be on Josh's!
我现在加现在加
他肯定就在JOSH的好友栏
Jamie, there's a roundabout here.
Can you please put the phone away?
Jamie这里有监控
你就不能等等再玩手机么
Jamie!
Yeah, he's on Josh's.
看吧我就说会在好友栏
Oh, my God. There he is.
Oh, my God!
看看看我找到了
我加了
You're not going to do it now?
你不会现在就加吧
Oh, my God, she did.
她是嘢
I friend requested him. Oh, my God.
好~好友申请中~嘢~~
Oh, my fucking God. I know how to
text and drive. I'm not a fucking idiot.
够了 我又不是傻子
我知道怎么一边开车一边手机的好不
Jamie, it's illegal to...
但这样不合法。。。
Oh, fuck, sorry.
哦！草 对不起
For heaven's sake.
天啊
Um, well, if you didn't talk to me
while I was trying to drive,
切 还不是因为你在旁边叽叽喳喳
there wouldn't be an issue.
You're going to cause an accident.
不然也不会出事
你要酿造交通餐具么！
Jamie, you need to focus.
JA'MIE你要集中注意力
Focus on yourself.
你管好自己去吧
Daddy's home! Hi, Daddy.
我爹居然在啊~爹 贵安哦
Hello, darling. How was school?
乖 小甜心 今天上课怎样
Why are you guys home early?
你们今天那么早下班
Hi, Mandy.
Hi, Jamie.
Why are you guys home?
你们为什么会在啊
We're flying interstate
late tonight, darl.
我们今晚要飞晚班国内航班 宝贝
Mandy's just helping me
organise some paperwork.
Mandy在帮我整理文件呢
Guys, this is Mandy, my dad's
assistant. She's really quiche.
姐妹们 她是我爸的小秘 她叫Mandy
很quiche吧
Um, Daddy, can we have pizza tonight?
爹哋 我们今晚能叫披萨嘛
Yeah, we can. Is that a new iPad,
Jamie? I hope that's not yours.
可以啊 等等Jamie
你手上那个是新爱屁股？不会是你买的吧
Yes, I told you I needed one for
school.
是我的 我不是告诉过你我上课要用么
Really? And how did you pay
for that? Your Amex.
真的？你哪来的钱啊
你的交易信托卡啊
Jamie, we said we'd discuss it.
You don't need the new one.
孩子 我不是跟你说过你不该买台新的么
The Amex card is
for emergencies only.
还有那卡是给你救急时用的
Pwease Daddy. It's educational.
求你了爹哋 这不是为了学业嘛！
Jamie, you need to check with your
father first before spending money.
Jamie你花钱应该跟你爸知会声啊
Shut up. Who asked you? New cover.
That's cool.
闭嘴 哪轮到你说话
哇~新外壳好美哦
Courtney doesn't even have
a laptop yet
Courtney她连个自己的手提都没有呢
and you're out there
buying iPads for yourself, Jamie.
Jamie你却乱花钱给你买爱屁股
Courtney doesn't have a laptop
because she is banned from using computers
Courtney没有手提是因为她之前盗用我微博账号
because she hacked into my Facebook,
so it's her own frigging fault.
所以才处罚她的
那时她咎由自取
Have you told your father
about schoolies week?
你跟你爹商量了毕业周的事情了么
Yeah, we booked Bali.
Again!
定了 去巴厘岛
啊~
This was to be discussed first,
Jamie. Which accommodation?
不是刚跟你说凡事要先预知一下么
那定了什么住处
The good resort.
华丽丽的那种
Are all your parents
agreeable to this, girls?
你们父母也就都同意了？
Yeah.
对啊
The bottom line is, you don't buy
things without our permission.
总之以后不许没有报备就随便花钱
Um, can you tell your loser wife
to stop bitching in my face?
那个 你能管管你那无能的老婆叫她闭嘴不
Don't speak to your mother like
that. That is disrespectful.
不许这样跟你妈说话
放尊重点
Where the fuck is my Coke Zero?
Did you drink it?
我的健怡可乐呢
你给喝了？
Fuck my life.
Don't touch my Coke Zero.
我苦逼娃啊！
不许随便喝我的健怡
Daddy...
爹哋
What?
什么
Can you make Jamie an iced coffee?
你能帮冲杯冷咖啡么？
Jamie is a high achiever.
She's a very beautiful girl.
我大女儿是个万人迷
She's everything that a
father would want in a daughter.
她是所有父亲所向往的那种女儿
but, that being said, we have to
rein her in every now and again.
但各种意义上说 我们还是必须好好管教她
I want one of your iced coffees
that you do.
我就想要你做的冰咖啡嘛
No, go away.
不行
Pwease, Daddy.
球你了
爹哋
I'm firsty.
人家渴啊
I'm not your slave.
我不是你的随从
Jamie thirsty. Come on, Daddy.
您女儿渴了 求你 爹爹
I'm not your slave. Go away.
我说了不做就是不做
I wuv you.
我要你嘛
-I've had a long day.
我今天很累 别闹
-I'll let you
be my friend on Facebook.
我会加你微博好友的哦
Go away.
不用谢谢
I'm blocking you from Facebook.
我绝对拉黑你
We want
the very best education for her,
我们很希望她能收到良好的教育
which I believe she's getting
at Hillford.
所以我们送她去读Hillford
Her Year 12 results
are vitally important,
而高中最后一年又尤其关键
and I expect a lot
from both my daughters.
我对我两个女儿都充满期望
We expect big things.
俺们 都很望女成凤
But, Jamie...
Man, she's special though.
但大姐她
唉 她真太有前途了
She's not only a very clever girl,
but she has proven herself
她不仅聪慧
to be a very kind
and compassionate girl as well.
而且还处处对自己高要求
努力做到坚韧不拔善良贤惠
'A nest of ferns
was her only place to rest.
‘巢蕨是她唯一能栖息的地方
It had been a thrilling day,
but a day she would rather forget.
今天过得无比漫长艰辛
但是她将永生难忘
The end.'
完
That's it. What do you say?
What do you say?
读完了 该你了
该你说了
Thank you, Ja'mie.
谢谢你
Alright. Goodnight, I'm going.
Bye, bye, bye, bye.
乖了 安 下了 88888
Oh, my God. He is so adorbs.
I know, how fucking cute is he?
天啊 他好萌
可不是
So how often do you read to him?
Like, every night, pretty much.
你那啥 经常给他读书么
额~基本每晚上啊就这样
I'm doing The Hunger Games at the
moment and he fucking loves it.
我现在在读【饥饿游戏】 他超爱的
He's pretty quiche
for an African guy.
他在非洲人那块算萌的了
I love it when he smiles
'cause he's all black
我最喜欢他笑得时候
and then, just bang,
this white thing.
因为刷白的牙齿一出现就华丽丽了
Yeah, this gleaming white thing
coming out of his mouth.
对啊 和黑皮肤一对比 铮亮铮亮的
He's so cute.
他好萌哦
I'm trying to get him to take his top
off, like, on Skype, but he won't.
我一直想叫他裸上身视频的 但他不肯
Can I sleep in the bed tonight?
I'm really sick of the mattress.
我今晚能睡床上么
我不想再打地铺了
I'm going to do
the lesbian prevention guard.
那我得先建起不许女同我防线
You're so funny, Ja'mie.
你好逗啊
I'm not even fucking joking.
I'm fucking serious.
我没逗你 我认真的
I'm not going to wake up with your
fingers in my vagina. 'Accidentally.'
我才不想明早一起来发现你手‘不小心地’
在我私处游动
Check your phone and see if Mitchell
has accepted your friend request?
快查查Mitchell通过你好友申请没
Yeah.
I hope he has.
对哦
He hasn't.
他还没
Oh!
I really want him to.
人家好想他加我哦
I'm starting to ship me
and Mitchell so badly.
我已经开始幻想我们搞一起了
What can I do to make him love me?
我该怎么让他爱上我啊
Oh, there's a Year 10 party coming
up. Would that be trag if we went?
对啊 高一新生要办派对 你觉得我们去会不会有点怪
Whose place is it at?
在哪办
It's at Jordan Kingsley's.
Jordan Kingsley家
All the Year 10 rugby guys are
going, so Mitchell will be there.
所有高一橄榄队员都会去 所以Mitchell也会在
I'd go, the Year 10s are hot
but it's kind of a bit creeps.
我要去 虽然里面都是萌物但总有点怪怪的
Fucking hell.
I've just thought of an idea.
草妹的
我刚想到一个好想法
What?
啥
Let's have a massive party here
at my house!
我们在我家搞个狂欢派对吧
Oh, my God. Are you serious?
哇！真的！？
Oh, my God!
Seriously, we haven't had a party
for months.
你想啊 我们好几个月都没有好好疯过了
Invite Mitchell,
invite all the Year 10s.
叫上Mitchell 还有所有高一的
How much does Ja'mie
have the best party house?
话说还有谁得家能比JAMIE家更适合呢
That is genius, Ja'mie.
Around the pool.
JAMIE你太棒了
我们要泳池趴
We can have, like, a bubble machine
and a smoke machine and a DJ.
接着配上泡泡机还有干冰机和DJ
And we can light up all the trees
with fairy lights and shit.
接着所有树丛都给亮得华丽丽
Costume one, or what?
I don't know.
主题趴还是啥好呢
Too much pressure.
妈呀 突然好大鸭梨
Yeah, dress really nice.
对啊 还要精心打扮
You can do slutty anyway.
我们可以走骚货路线
Want to look classy.
但我比较像走高贵
Fuck. Oh, my God.
This is the best idea ever.
草~草草~
我太聪明了
Should I ask my dad?
我们去求情我爹吧
Yes, let's go now.
好 立马
Oh, my God.
天啊~~
Daddy?
爹哋
Can I have a party, like,
just us girls, this Friday?
我们可以周五全女班办个派对么
Just all of us?
No. No parties.
-只有我们几个
-不不行
Please? I really want one.
No. It's Year 12.
-求你了 我好想搞
-你今年高三 不许
I'm not having a bunch of teenagers,
我才不想让一堆我不认识的熊孩子
especially ones I don't know,
in this house.
跑我家撒野
Daddy, please.
爹哋 求你嘛
Jamie can be very persuasive
when she wants to be.
Jamie每次有求于我总会使劲招数
She has this habit of biting me
on the shoulder
她有一绝招就是咬我的肩部
when she wants to get her own way.
这招一用必灵
She's done it
ever since she was little.
她从小就学会了
It gets me every time, eh?
结果就成为她有求必应招
She can be very flirtatious,
you know.
她有时候真的很会让我脸红心跳
你懂我说的
Daddy. Pwease.
球你了 爹爹
Full adult supervision.
And no alcohol, that we know of.
全程成年人监控
和一如往常的不喝酒
No alcohol.
不喝酒
No alcohol. No.
不喝 绝不
Boys?
男孩子呢
Um, no boys.
就女生
Maybe a couple.
又或许会有十来个男的
Come on!
来嘛
Jhyll, are you agreeable to this?
Jhyll你觉得呢
I've heard things can get out of
hand. I don't know.
我听说一疯起来会很可怕 我拿不定主意
Let them do it. It'll be fun.
就依他们一下啦 没啥不好的
- You're only a teenager once.
-青春一去不复返啊
- Yes.
-对嘛
Yes! Go, Mandy.
Mandy你是最棒的
I suppose... Alright.
那  好吧
On condition...
附带条件
Yeah, what?
是 啥
..that you focus on your studies
afterwards.
你要给加倍念书
Yeah, whatever. Oh, my God.
So we can do it?
知道啦 那就说定罗
Yes, OK.
嗯
Yes! Oh, my God!
哇~！！赛高
And no adults are allowed. You guys
have to stay upstairs the whole time.
家长不许搅和
你们只能一直呆在楼上
Oh, my fucking God. I can't believe
we're having a party here.
妈妈咪呀 我们要在我家办趴啦！！
It's gonna be so fucking good.
太神啦
Check you phone, check your phone!
Oh, my God.
快看手机手机
天啊
Mitchell Ward has accepted your
friend request!
Mitchell Ward同意加你好友
Seriously!
天啊~~
This party is going to be
so fucking good!
这回可以玩疯了
Oh, my God!
太好了
Seriously, I'm gonna get my crunk on
so bad.
到时候我要将音箱开到尽头
Next time on
Ja'mie: Private School Girl.
Last night, he sends me a dick pic.
Oh, my God.
Gross!
They're choosing the best dance soloists to
perform in front of the wholeschool.
Are you fucking serious?
Are you trying to sound bad?
We sound fine. Grow some tits
and shut your fat face.
So I told Josh and all his friends
to meet us after choir practice.
OK, quick, get in, get in.
I didn't think you were gonna come.
Some of us are straight in here.
Don't look.
Fucking delete it, you stupid slut.
Subtitles by MemoryOnSmells
http://UKsubtitles.ru.